

HUYNH NGOC TUAN CUONG



May 19,1993



huynhcuong19051993@gmail.com



+84 354 820 477



76/67A Bach Dang, Ward 24, Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City



ABOUT ME

An expert in e-commerce, with experience and enthusiasm via working in e-commerce projects of Alibaba Group in Vietnam. Able to work well independently and as part of an Internet business team. In recent years I have focused on e-commerce and international (digital) marketing.



SKILLS

Public Speaking

Leadership

Working in group

Negotiation

Communication

Problem-Solving



- B English Certificate
- Logistic certification
- Certificate B computerization



WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present AMERASIAN SHIPPING LOGISTICS CORP

E-commerce Sales Specialist

- Find and develop relationships with customers who are SMEs with potential products in exporting to the international market.
- Advise customers the benefits of exporting products to the international market through the Alibaba.com ecommerce flat-form as well as the logistic services of the company assisting the customer.
- Collect, capture, analyze market information, and competitor information.
- Organize and implement events, press conferences, meetings, etc.
- Implement and monitor implementation of policies for customers, coordinate with Team Service to implement care and customer support after the sale.

2017 - 2018 NINA TRADING AND SERVICES CO., LTD

Sales executive

- Search for new customers
- Advise clients on the benefits and service packages which the company provides
- Guide customers to use, demo, support customers in the process of experience and use of the service

2017 - 2018 ANH TAI SMARTPHONE STORE

Sales executive

- Advise customers about smartphones and repair services at the shop
- Support customer when they have problem with smartphone



EDUCATION

2011 – 2015 Hutech University of Technology Industrial Electricity

2016 – 2018 Hutech University of Technology
Master of Business Administration